Contact

Incnicolecromwell@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/nicolecromwell (LinkedIn) nicolecromwellart.com (Company)

Top Skills

Healthcare

Hospitals

Nursing

Certifications

Clinical Nurse Leader

CCRN

CNRN

Nicole Cromwell

RN, MSN, CNL, CCRN nicolecromwellart.com

Pacific Grove, California

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Sepsis, Stroke, Patient Safety, Electronic Medical Record (EMR), and Critical Care Nursing. Strong healthcare services professional with a Clinical Nurse Leader Master's Degree from the University of San Francisco.

Experience

Stanford Health Care

17 years 6 months

Critical Care Response Team February 2015 - Present (5 years 5 months)

Palo Alto, CA

Respond to all Rapid Reponse, stroke, and Code Blue calls throughout the hospital. Function as a team member evaluating patients for higher level of care needs. Expert IV and feeding tube insertion skills. Ability to float and function independently in the Emergency Department, ICU, and Recovery Room environment.

Critical Care Registered Nurse

January 2003 - 2015 (12 years)

Intensive Care Unit

Provide expert care for a variety of acutely ill patients in a 33 bed fast paced medical, surgical, neurosurgical, neurological, trauma, and transplant intensive care unit. Manage complex care for patients on cardiac monitors, cardiac drip medications, CRRT, arctic sun, and advanced neurological monitoring.

Flight Nurse

2003 - 2005 (2 years)

Palo Alto, CA

Provided critical care transport for adult and pediatric patients by inter-facility and scene calls throughout Northern and Central California.

Community Hospital of the Monterey Peninsula Emergency Room Nurse 1999 - 2002 (3 years)

Carmel, CA

Provided triage and emergency care to adult and pediatric population of Monterey County.

Education

University of San Francisco

Master's Degree, Clinical Nurse Leader · (2012 - 2014)

Monterey Peninsula College Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse